{"data":[{"question":"That singer has been _____ several talk shows recently.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- Prepositions of Place: at, in, on\n- At for a point: at the corner,at the bus stop,at the door,at the top of the page,at the front desk...\n- In for an enclosed space: in the garden, in London, in a box, in my wallet...\n- On for a surface: on the wall, on the floor, on a page...","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"39","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"2"},{"question":"Heat two tablespoons of olive oil ____ a skillet over medium heat.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- Prepositions of Place: at, in, on\n- At for a point: at the corner,at the bus stop,at the door,at the top of the page,at the front desk...\n- In for an enclosed space: in the garden, in London, in a box, in my wallet...\n- On for a surface: on the wall, on the floor, on a page...","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"39","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"2"},{"question":"We're moving house ____ two months.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"1","explain":"\n\n- Prepositions of Place: at, in, on\n- At for a point: at the corner,at the bus stop,at the door,at the top of the page,at the front desk...\n- In for an enclosed space: in the garden, in London, in a box, in my wallet...\n- On for a surface: on the wall, on the floor, on a page...","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"39","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"2"},{"question":"Some people say the ghost appears in the castle _____ the stroke of midnight.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- Prepositions of Place: at, in, on\n- At for a point: at the corner,at the bus stop,at the door,at the top of the page,at the front desk...\n- In for an enclosed space: in the garden, in London, in a box, in my wallet...\n- On for a surface: on the wall, on the floor, on a page...","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"39","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"2"},{"question":"Put the papers ___ the desk please.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n Prepositions of Place: at, in, on\n- At for a point: at the corner, at the bus stop, at the door, at the top of the page, at the front desk...\n- In for an enclosed space: in the garden, in London, in a box, in my wallet, in a industry...\n- On for a surface: on the wall, on the floor, on a page...\n\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"39","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"2"},{"question":"Christian isn't here. He's ____ work.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n Prepositions of Place: at, in, on\n- At for a point: at the corner, at the bus stop, at the door, at the top of the page, at the front desk...\n- In for an enclosed space: in the garden, in London, in a box, in my wallet, in a industry...\n- On for a surface: on the wall, on the floor, on a page...\n\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"39","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"2"},{"question":"Senator Johnson spoke _____ the memorial service last Friday.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"1","explain":"\n\n Prepositions of Place: at, in, on\n- At for a point: at the corner, at the bus stop, at the door, at the top of the page, at the front desk...\n- In for an enclosed space: in the garden, in London, in a box, in my wallet, in a industry...\n- On for a surface: on the wall, on the floor, on a page...\n\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"39","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"2"},{"question":"The banks open _____ 9am.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n Prepositions of Place: at, in, on\n- At for a point: at the corner, at the bus stop, at the door, at the top of the page, at the front desk...\n- In for an enclosed space: in the garden, in London, in a box, in my wallet, in a industry...\n- On for a surface: on the wall, on the floor, on a page...\n\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"39","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"2"},{"question":"Julia's birthday is ____ November","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"1","explain":"\n\n- Prepositions of Place: at, in, on\n- At for a point: at the corner, at the bus stop, at the door, at the top of the page, at the front desk...\n- In for an enclosed space: in the garden, in London, in a box, in my wallet, in a industry...\n- On for a surface: on the wall, on the floor, on a page...\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"39","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"2"},{"question":"There is a list of irregular verbs _____ the appendix.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n Prepositions of Place: at, in, on\n- At for a point: at the corner, at the bus stop, at the door, at the top of the page, at the front desk...\n- In for an enclosed space: in the garden, in London, in a box, in my wallet, in a industry...\n- On for a surface: on the wall, on the floor, on a page...\n\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"39","subcategorylv2":"1","type":"2"}]}